{ "questions" :
  [
    {"question" : "Use one word for the arguments arg1, arg2",
     "answer" : "*args",
     "info" : "def method( *args); The splat operator is used to handle methods which have a variable parameter list."},

    {"question" : "Set contents - contents = File.open(file) - to the 5th character",
     "answer" : "contents.seek(5)",
     "info" : ""},

    {"question" : "Set contents back to the start of the stream",
     "answer" : "contents.rewind",
     "info" : ""},

    {"question" : "Create a heredoc with the word \"there\"",
     "answer" : "<<END there END",
     "info" : "A \"heredoc\" is used to create a multi-line string"},

    {"question" : "Create and array of letters from \"word\"",
     "answer" : "'word'.split('')",
     "info" : "word.split() = ['w', 'o', 'r', 'd']"},

    {"question" : "Create an array of words from str = \"Some words\"",
     "answer" : "str.split(' ')" ,
     "info" : "str.split() = ['some', 'words']"},

    {"question" : "Alphabetize arr = ['do', 're', 'me']",
     "answer" : "arr.sort",
     "info" : "[9, 1, 4].sort = [1, 4, 9]"},

    {"question" : "Maintain the array's new order",
     "answer" : "arr.sort!",
     "info" : "Or arr = arr.sort => ['do', 'me', 're']"},

    {"question" : "Remove the first element from arr and set it to \"x\"",
     "answer" : "x = arr.shift",
     "info" : "x = do"},

    {"question" : "arr.count",
     "answer" : "2" ,
     "info" : "['me', 're']"},

    {"question" : "Remove the last element from arr and set it to \"y\"",
     "answer" : "y = arr.pop",
     "info" : "y = re"},

    {"question" : "arr.count",
     "answer" : "1" ,
     "info" : "['me']"},

    {"question" : "END",
     "answer" : "END",
     "info" : "********* 4.json is next **********\n"}
  ]
}